## **Curriculum Vitae**

**Personal information** 

First name: Mika

Last name: Grootenboer

Address: Dordrecht, Netherlands

Phone number: -

Email:

Birthdate: 19-12-1998, Dordrecht

Nationality: Netherlands

Gender: Man Driver license: B, AM

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/mika-grootenboer-3b8b84145/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/mika-grootenboer-3b8b84145/</a>

Portfolio: <a href="https://mikagrootenboer.nl">https://mikagrootenboer.nl</a>

Personality: My name is Mika Grootenboer, I'm 21 years old and currently a fourth-year

Computer Science student at the university of Rotterdam. I'm a hard worker

and I'm always open to learn new stuff.

**Education** 

2016-present Bachelor Software Engineering, fourth year

**Rotterdam University of Applied Sciences** 

2011-2016 HAVO Economy and Society

Stedelijk Dalton Lyceum Kapteynweg, Dordrecht

**Work experience** 

2018-2019 intern Devops Redkiwi, Rotterdam

Together with a small team of four responsible for the servers and working

on the automation of updates.

2016-2019 AGF collaborator Jumbo, Dordrecht

Responsible for the AGF (potatoes, vegetables and fruit) department,

working together with a group of ten colleagues.

2012-2016 Spotta folder deliverer, Dordrecht

Delivering flyers on Monday and Tuesday in my neighborhood.

Other informatie

Languages: Netherlands Native language

English Good

Computer Knowledge: Basic knowledge of HTML, CSS, C#, F#, Python, SQL, Ansible, PHP, Nginx, Kali,

Ubuntu, Windows

Project management: Basic knowledge of Agile/ Scrum

**Hobbies and Interest** 

Security, Sporting, gaming and reading